<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
	<atom:link href="http://www.slitaz.org/en/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<title>Slitaz GNU/Linux RSS feed</title>
	<link>http://www.slitaz.org/en/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en</language>
	<description>
		SliTaz GNU/Linux News
	</description>
	<copyright>Copyright © www.slitaz.org - GNU gpl</copyright>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2009 11:30:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
	
	<image>
		<title>Slitaz GNU/Linux (fr)</title>
		<url>http://www.slitaz.org/pics/artwork/slitaz-spider-48x48.png</url>
		<link>http://www.slitaz.org/fr/</link>
	</image>
	
	<item>
		<title>19 May 2009 - SliTaz at LinuxDays 2009 (Geneva)</title>
		<link>http://www.slitaz.org/en/asso/</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">http://2009.linuxdays.ch/</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2009 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<description>
	During the LinuxDays show in Switzerland, the association will have 
	a booth in the Association Village and a lecture will be given on 
	Wednesday morning. The lecture is a case study with a corporate view 
	based on using a "SliTaz Business Server" with a switchboard,
	integrated ERP, mail, LDAP, etc... During the 3 days, the exhibition 
	stand will be manned by members of the SliTaz project. The booth will 
	offer demonstrations, including the creation of bootable USB keys 
	(LiveUSB) and cdroms. The LinuxDays LiveCD will contain a selection 
	of software designed for mobile use. The exhibition lounge will also 
	have a forum and we will gladly answer any questions. So feel free 
	to visit us! Information can be found on SliTaz Labs: 
	http://labs.slitaz.org/wiki/events/2009-linuxdays and the exhibition 
	website: http://2009.linuxdays.ch/
		</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>16 April 2009 - SliTaz GNU/Linux 2.0 Release</title>
		<link>http://www.slitaz.org/en/get/</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.slitaz.org/</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 April 2009 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<description>
	The SliTaz project are proud to announce the release of the new 
	stable version of the distribution - SliTaz GNU/Linux 2.0. This new 
	version is the result of one year of community work and provides an 
	ultra lightweight, fast, scalable and stable operating system. SliTaz 
	provides a complete graphical desktop in less than 30MB, applications 
	required for a reliable and robust server environment and 1400 easily 
	installable software packages in a few clicks of the mouse. This new 
	version offers the automounting of partitions (NTFS compliant), wifi 
	support, an office respecting the Freedesktop.org standards (drag 
	and drop), network booting with gPXE and boot.slitaz.org, automatic 
	detection of USB and PCI devices, a GUI package manager and control 
	center, and various graphical tools to manage the distribution. 
	The creation of USB media and bootable LiveCD flavors is also 
	simplified and greatly improved. The core LiveCD includes Firefox 
	3.0.8, gFTP, LostIRC, ePDFView, mtPaint, Transmission, Osmo and 
	Alsaplayer. The website documentation has been updated and you can 
	read the release notes included in the distribution for more details 
	on this stable version. SliTaz GNU/Linux 2.0 is now downloadable 
	from the official mirrors of the project.
		</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>27 March 2009 - Labs and new mirrors</title>
		<link>http://www.slitaz.org/en/</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">http://labs.slitaz.org/</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 April 2009 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<description>
	Continually seeking to improve the distribution and the services we 
	offer, we are proud to announce the launch of SliTaz Labs. This 
	platform makes it possible for contributors to collaborate more 
	effectively, report bugs or request new features. The Labs provide 
	each project with a wiki, a bug/issues tracker, news, etc. The 
	laboratories provide an overview of activity on the project and track 
	the release of regular updates. Register to participate and leave a 
	comment. The project is also proud to announce 2 new mirrors: In 
	Switzerland, hosted by SWITCHmirror (10 Gbits/s) and hosted in China 
	by LupaWorld, thanks for supporting us.
		</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>20 March 2009 - SliTaz at Solutionslinux 2009 (Paris)</title>
		<link>http://www.slitaz.org/en/</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.solutionslinux.fr/</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2009 16:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<description>
	The SliTaz project will be present at Solutionslinux 2009 in Paris. 
	The stand will be hosted by 3 members of the team during the 3 day 
	event and several other contributors will be present at some point. 
	There you will have the opportunity to test various machines, EeePC 
	for example, create a USB key (bring one with you) or to buy USB keys 
	or bootable LiveCDs. You can also learn about the project and make 
	contact with members of the association and the development team. 
		</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Cooking 20090228 - New Cooking</title>
		<link>http://www.slitaz.org/en/get/#cooking</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.slitaz.org/en/get/</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 10:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<description>
	Getting ready for the next stable release! - The SliTaz project is 
	proud to publish a new Cooking version with a lot of bug fixes, 
	updates, improvements and new features. PCI/USB device auto-detection 
	is now handled by Tazhw and firmware can be installed in one click 
	through a graphical interface. Tazndis also has a simple GUI which 
	lets you manage Windows drivers in a user friendly interface. The 
	graphical packages manager is also much simpler to use and LiveUSB 
	media such as a USB key can easily be created through a box. Netbox 
	displays all interfaces and the new Wifibox can connect to wireless 
	essids, manage favorite networks and configure card drivers manually 
	or through Tazhw. The desktop has a GUI to enable or disable 
	applications started with an Openbox session and Ivman with 
	desktopkbox provides a lightweight notification system. You can 
	download this new ISO image from one of the official mirrors of the 
	website.
		</description>
	</item>

</channel>
</rss>
