<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
	<atom:link href="http://www.slitaz.org/en/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<title>Slitaz GNU/Linux RSS feed</title>
	<link>http://www.slitaz.org/en/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en</language>
	<description>
		SliTaz GNU/Linux News
	</description>
	<copyright>Copyright © www.slitaz.org - GNU gpl</copyright>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 22:50:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
	
	<item>
		<title>Cooking 20080716 - Web boot and MPlayer</title>
		<link>http://www.slitaz.org/en/get/#cooking</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.slitaz.org/en/get/</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 22:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<description>
	SliTaz project members are proud to announce the availability of a new
	Cooking version, including many new features and bug fixes. This version 
	provides the boot option web which lets you boot SliTaz from the internet 
	using gPXE from boot.slitaz.org. This new unique service offers the 
	possibility to use SliTaz in Live mode (all in RAM), using the Live options 
	to store your data permanently and preconfigure the system. This new Cooking 
	takes an extra 3 Mb so we can provide: a multimedia player with MPlayer, a 
	notes manager with Notecase, a new version of Tazpkg package manager with 
	md5sum support, XFS filesystem support built into the Kernel, a 'man' command 
	and a few updates. This version requires at least 160 Mb to boot and run 
	properly, we offer loram flavors for machines with less resources.
		</description>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Cooking 20080626 - New Kernel</title>
		<link>http://www.slitaz.org/en/</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.slitaz.org/en/get/</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2008 10:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<description>
	Summer time is here and also the new Cooking from the 26 June. A lot
	of work has been done to improve user experience. This Cooking version
	provides a new Kernel (2.6.25.5) with many new built-in drivers and 
	modules, linux package was also split to have a fairly modular Kernel.
	Default user has changed to tux and the new option 
	user=name lets you choose the default user name. Most
	of the Slitaz utils and tools have been improved: tazpkgbox provides
	some new commands for package management and bootfloppybox can be used in
	text mode, Netbox wifi and PPPoE support are now both working well and
	a new function called zeroconf is available. Most packages are up-to-date
	and Firefox 3.0 is part of the 25.2 Mb ISO. Cooking version can be
	downloaded from SliTaz mirror. Bugs can be reported on SliTaz Bug 
	Tracking System.
		</description>
	</item>
	
    <item>
		<title>Cooking 20080518 - LinuxDays.ch</title>
		<link>http://www.slitaz.org/en/</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.slitaz.org/en/get/</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 23:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<description>
	SliTaz team is proud to announce the availability of a new Cooking
	LiveCD ISO image providing huge changes from the stable release.
	SliTaz now uses Openbox as its default Window Manager, desktop icons let
	you launch your favorite applications and manage files and dbus and hal
	will automatically mount removable media such as USB keys or Hard disks.
	Packages can now be managed through the graphical Packages Manager
	Tazpkgbox and mountbox and netbox are now much more usable and complete.
	The LiveCD now offers: lua, a desktop search engine with searchmonkey,
	system information with Hardinfo, task management with LXTasks and a
	password and clipboard manager. All the major packages have been updated -
	SliTaz now uses a new toolchain using the last glibc-2.7, GTK 2.12.9
	and Firefox 3.0 RC1! You will now find 580 packages on the mirror
	including wireless support for the kernel and the necessary tools 
	for a manual connection or one managed by SliTaz netbox. This new announced
	Cooking version can be downloaded from SliTaz mirror. Note: This version is 
	going to be used at the LinuxDay.ch in Geneva, Switzerland.
		</description>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>March 2008 - SliTaz GNU/Linux 1.0 release</title>
		<link>http://www.slitaz.org/en/get/#stable</link>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.slitaz.org/en/get/</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<description>
	The SliTaz contributors team are proud to announce the publication of SliTaz
	GNU/Linux 1.0. This is the first stable release after 2 years of work. The
	system is distributed as a bootable LiveCD of 24.8 MB providing a fully
	featured desktop environment and a generous selection of multi-use applications.
	SliTaz GNU/Linux 1.0 uses the Linux Kernel 2.6.24.2, providing Firefox 2.0.0.12,
	Rsync 3.0.0, Gparted 0.3.5 and sound support with Alsa 1.0.16. The distribution
	lets you listen to music, surf the Web, edit a video studio and much more
	with the 448 available packages that can be installed with our own
	package manager Tazpkg. The LiveCD lets you create a custom distro or a LiveUSB
	device in one single command. Security updates are provided by the project and
	popular packages like Firefox will also get upgraded for functionality. You
	can get SliTaz GNU/Linux 1.0 from the Web site download page. Read the Release 
	Notes for more detailed information on this stable version.
		</description>
	</item>

</channel>
</rss>
